Vivien Kellems Papers 1992.0033
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
Vivien Kellems Papers
undated, 1879-1976.
1992.0033
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
82.75 Linear feet
Vivien Kellems, Connecticut businesswoman and activist, served as president of the Kellems Cable Grip Company into the early 1960s. She also devoted herself to challenging the United States Government on issues such as personal rights during war time, business tax withholding from employees, inflated singles income tax and fair voting procedures.
Kellems, Vivien.
Box 41
Box 42
Box 54
Box 44
Box 22
Box 21
Box 24
Box 30
Box 26
Box 25
Box 28
Box 29
Box 32
Box 31
Box 34
Box 33
Box 37
Box 36
Box 39
Box 38
Box 51
Box 43
Box 23
Box 53
Box 40
Box 35
Box 50
Box 49
Box 3
Box 4
Box 1
Box 2
Box 19
Box 20
Box 17
Box 18
Box 16
Box 45
Box 46
Box 47
Box 12
Box 13
Box 14
Box 15
Box 8
Box 9
Box 10
Box 11
Box 27
Box 5
Box 6
Box 7
Box 55
Box 56
Box 48
Box 52
Box 58
Box 59
Box 57
Box 62
Box 63
Box 60
Box 61
Biography
Vivien Kellems was born 7 June 1896 in Des Moines, Iowa, to David Clinton and Louisa Flint Kellems. Shortly after her birth, her parents, both Christian Ministers, moved their family to the west coast and settled in Eugene, Oregon. Being the only girl of a family with seven children, Vivien developed a rugged and competitive personality from a young age. Attending the University of Oregon, she participated as the only female on the debate team. Vivien Kellems obtained a bachelors degree in 1918 and a masters degree in economics shortly there after. Following graduation, she moved east to New York City in pursuit of a doctorate from Columbia University and the University of Edinburgh.
While in New York, an improvement on an existing cable grip was made by her older brother, Edgar E. Kellems, which he patented in the late 1920s. Using the patent as the focal point, Ms. Kellems founded Kellems Cable Grips, Inc. in 1927 and eventually moved her plant to Stonington, Connecticut. Successfully operating the company as president for over thirty years, the company's devices were used most notably during the construction of the Chrysler Building, George Washington Bridge, and also played an important role in production of wire and artillery shell grips used during World War II.
In her personal life, Vivien Kellems encountered various struggles for justice as she fought for women's equality, equal suffrage along party lines and tax reform. As a member of the Liberty Belles, Vivien led by example as the group encouraged equality of women in the home, workplace and society. Running as an independent candidate for senate, Ms. Kellems protested strict party line voting that only required a single lever pull rather than voting individually by candidate. Through civil disobedience, Vivien Kellems made her position known as she sat in a voting booth for nine hours straight before she fainted from exhaustion. With a degree in economics, unfair taxation by the government was at the forefront of Vivien Kellems' battles. In 1948, alongside of her business partner and brother David Kellems, she protested against withholding taxes from her employees' checks claiming, "if they wanted me to be their (tax) agent, they'd have to pay me, and I want a badge." After a lengthy court battle ensued, it was found that the Kellems Co. would go bankrupt if they continued to not withhold taxes. Admitting defeat, Vivien would later fight against the singles income tax law that was enacted after World War II. In the law, citizens who were not married paid twice the amount of income tax than did those citizens of equal earnings who were married. In protest, from 1965 until her death, Vivien Kellems would merely send in tax forms with no pertinent information instead sending a blank form with her signature. Coming close to victory many times in the United States Supreme Court during the first half of the 1970s, Ms. Kellems' fight in this case ended in vain, as she died before her final appeal was heard in 1975.
General note
Published Works:
Toil, Taxes and Troubles. E.P. Dutton & Co., Inc., 1952.
Scope and Content
The collection contains extensive materials from Vivien Kellems' personal life, business career, extended family, real estate endeavors and various activist movements of which she was an advocate. As the collection spans all of Ms. Kellems' adult life, it provides an in-depth and thorough into how each component of her life was handled. Included are legal documents, speeches, photographs, agendas, itineraries, minutes, payroll, business records, business checks, personal checks, notes, advertisements, newspaper clippings, memorabilia and correspondence to and from business associates, colleagues, fans of her cause, and family members.
Arrangement
As best as possible the arrangement follows that established by Ms. Kellems.
Series I: Family Papers (undated, 1883-1975) is composed of correspondence and personal materials relating to the extended family of Vivien Kellems. Arranged alphabetically by family member, contents include correspondence, legal documents, and memorabilia. The series includes correspondence with Vivien Kellems' mother, father, four of six brothers (one died in infancy, one died in World War I), four sisters-in-law, four aunts, one uncle, six nephews, two nieces, and ten distant relatives. (Please see attached genealogical chart to identify specific individuals or family names. Due to software incapabilities, genealogical information cannot be displayed electronically, please contact the curator for a copy.)
Series II: Personal Papers ( undated, 1928-1975 ) contains letters to and from friends, business aquitances, employees and fans of Ms. Kellems and her work. The series is arranged chronologically and alphabetically therein. Although some files are topical in nature, others contain correspondence between Ms. Kellems and the residents of a particular state. A box containing photographs, negatives and ephemera and memorabilia is also included in this series.
Series III: Activism ( undated, 1879-1975 ) contains correspondence, studies, publications, clippings, scrapbooks and similar materials related to Ms. Kellems' involvement in politics, Equal Rights Amendment, tax issues among other topics.
Series IV: Real Estate ( undated, 1872-1976 ) includes correspondence and financial records pertaining to various pieces of property.
Series V: Business Records ( undated, 1905-1963 (all dates noted are circa) contains materials pertaining to activities, issues, functions and the workings of the Kellems companies. predominantly correspondence and legal records, the series also contains information about patents, publicity, advertising and associated businesses.
Separated Material
The following materials have been separated from the collection and cataloged:
Autobiography of a Catholic Anarchist Dodd C 10196
Life and Times of John Birch Dodd A 9721
Meditations of Joseph Stalin Dodd A 9719
None dare call it conspiracy Dodd A 9720
Our invisible Government made visible Dodd A 9725
Russia and the Big Red Lie Dodd C 10192
Restrictions on Access
There are no access restrictions on this collection.
Custodial History
Inherited by nephew, Vangelder Kellems, from the estate of Vivien Kellems.
Acquisition Information
Donated by Vangelder Kellems in 1992.
Related Material
Archives & Special Collections has a substantial collection of materials pertaining to Connecticut business as well as the papers of civic activists. For detailed information on these collections please contact the curator or ask at the Reading Room desk.
Kellems family.; Kellems, Vivien.; Administrative Records.; Blueprints.; Books.; Connecticut--Business, industries, and trades--Cable manufacturing.; Contracts.; Correspondence.; Electric wire and cable industry--Connecticut--Stonington.; Financial Records.; Interviews.; Lawsuits.; Manufacturing.; Maps.; Minutes.; Newspapers.; Notes.; Obituaries.; Patents.; Petitions.; Photocopies.; Photographs.; Plats.; Posters.; Press releases.; Publications.; Speeches.; Stonington (Conn.)--Business, industries, and trades--Cable manufacturing.; Suffrage--United States.; Taxation--United States.; Typescripts.; Women chief executive officers--United States--Biography.; Women's rights--United States.
- Series I: Family Papers, undated, 1883-1975
  - Andrews, Kenneth, 1966 (Box 1:, Folder 1)
  - Bailey, Anna, undated, 1939-1944 (Box 1:, Folder 2)
  - Bailey, Anna: Memoirs, 1972 (Box 1:, Folder 3)
  - Bailey, Ed & Helen, 1941-1954 (Box 1:, Folder 4)
  - Bernhard, Ann, 1949-1951 (Box 1:, Folder 5)
  - Doran, Jon, 1974 (Box 1:, Folder 6)
  - Holmes, Clara & John, 1950,1951,1959 (Box 1:, Folder 7)
  - Kellam, Irene, 1951 (Box 1:, Folder 8)
  - Kellems Family, 1952-1954 (Box 1:, Folder 9)
  - Kellems, David Clinton, 1951-1951 (Box 1:, Folder 10)
  - Kellems, David Clinton, II, undated,1955-1974 (Box 1:, Folder 11)
  - Kellems, David L., undated,1936-1974 (Box 1:, Folder 12)
  - Kellems, Edgar: Patent Royalties, 1935-1936 (Box 1:, Folder 13)
  - Kellems, Edgar: Patent Royalties, 1937 (Box 1:, Folder 14)
  - Kellems, Edgar, 1938-1945 (Box 1:, Folder 15)
  - Kellems, Edgar, 1946-1953 (Box 1:, Folder 16)
  - Kellems, Edgar: Sympathy Letters, 1953-1954 (Box 1:, Folder 17)
  - Kellems, Edgar: Regarding Estate, 1954 (Box 1:, Folder 18)
  - Kellems, Edgar: Patented Inventions, 1883-1953 (Box 1:, Folder 19)
  - Kellems, Faye, 1939-1949 (Box 1:, Folder 20)
  - Kellems, Faye, 1950-1958 (Box 1:, Folder 21)
  - Kellems, Faye: Regarding Homer's Death, 1959 January - June (Box 1:, Folder 22)
  - Kellems, Faye: Regarding Homer's Death, 1959 July - December (Box 1:, Folder 23)
  - Kellems, Faye, 1960 (Box 1:, Folder 24)
  - Kellems, Faye, 1961-1962 (Box 1:, Folder 25)
  - Kellems, Florence, 1953 (Box 1:, Folder 26)
  - Kellems, George & Elizabeth, undated,1948-1952 (Box 1:, Folder 27)
  - Kellems, Hazel Dean, 1936-1945 (Box 1:, Folder 28)
  - Kellems, Hazel Dean, 1946-1955 (Box 1:, Folder 29)
  - Kellems, Hazel Dean, undated,1956-1974 (Box 1:, Folder 30)
  - Kellems, Homer, 1938-1952 (Box 1:, Folder 31)
  - Kellems, Homer, 1954-1958 (Box 1:, Folder 32)
  - Kellems, Homer: Letters and Notes of Bereavement, 1959 (Box 1:, Folder 33)
  - Kellems, Homer: Sympathy Cards, 1959 (Box 1:, Folder 34)
  - Kellems, Homer: Sympathy Letters (A - D), 1959 (Box 1:, Folder 35)
  - Kellems, Homer: Sympathy Letters (F - N), 1959 (Box 1:, Folder 36)
  - Kellems, Homer: Sympathy Letters (O - Z), 1959 (Box 1:, Folder 37)
  - Kellems, Inez, 1937-1974 (Box 1:, Folder 38)
  - Kellems, Jesse, 1931-1939 (Box 1:, Folder 39)
  - Kellems, Jesse, 1940-1949 (Box 1:, Folder 40)
  - Kellems, Jesse, 1950-1954 (Box 1:, Folder 41)
  - Kellems, Jesse, 1955-1959 (Box 1:, Folder 42)
  - Kellems, Jesse, 1960-1969 (Box 1:, Folder 43)
  - Kellems, Kaye & Ros Andrews, 1947-1973 (Box 1:, Folder 44)
  - Kellems, Kaye & Kenneth, 1939-1941 (Box 1:, Folder 45)
  - Kellems, Kenneth Clinton & Pat, 1956-1974 (Box 1:, Folder 46)
  - Kellems, Kenneth, 1918 (Box 1:, Folder 47)
  - Kellems, Louisa Flint: Letters Home While on Undergraduate Speaking Tour, undated,1915-1917 (Box 2:, Folder 48)
  - Kellems, Louisa Flint, 1936-1937 (Box 2:, Folder 49)
  - Kellems, Louisa Flint, 1938 (Box 2:, Folder 50)
  - Kellems, Louisa Flint, 1939 (Box 2:, Folder 51)
  - Kellems, Louisa Flint, 1940 (Box 2:, Folder 52)
  - Kellems, Louisa Flint, 1941 (Box 2:, Folder 53)
  - Kellems, Louisa Flint, 1942 (Box 2:, Folder 54)
  - Kellems, Louisa Flint, 1943 (Box 2:, Folder 55)
  - Kellems, Louisa Flint, 1944 (Box 2:, Folder 56)
  - Kellems, Louisa Flint, 1945 (Box 2:, Folder 57)
  - Kellems, Louisa Flint, 1946 (Box 2:, Folder 58)
  - Kellems, Louisa Flint, 1947 (Box 2:, Folder 59)
  - Kellems, Louisa Flint, 1948-1949 (Box 2:, Folder 60)
  - Kellems, Louisa Flint: Items Relating to Death, 1949-1951 (Box 2:, Folder 61)
  - Kellems, Louisa Flint: Letters of Condolence (A - K), 1949-1950 (Box 2:, Folder 62)
  - Kellems, Louisa Flint: Letters of Condolence (K - Z), 1949-1950 (Box 2:, Folder 63)
  - Kellems, Louisa Flint: Regarding Estate, 1943,1950-1953 (Box 2:, Folder 64)
  - Kellems, Randolph & Debbie, 1954-1973 (Box 2:, Folder 65)
  - Kellems, Tille, undated,1938-1974 (Box 2:, Folder 66)
  - Kellems, Tille: Vehichle Accident, 1951 (Box 2:, Folder 67)
  - Kellems, Vangelder & David's Life Insurance, 1951 (Box 3:, Folder 68)
  - Kellems, Vangelder "Van" & Jacqui, undated,1955-1974 (Box 3:, Folder 69)
  - Kellems, Vivienne & Jack Proctor, 1940-1972 (Box 3:, Folder 70)
  - Kellom, Rex E., 1952 (Box 3:, Folder 71)
  - McMahan, Elizabeth, 1937-1938 (Box 3:, Folder 72)
  - McMahan, Elizabeth: Regarding Estate, 1939 (Box 3:, Folder 73)
  - McMahan, Vira, 1939 (Box 3:, Folder 74)
  - Moore, Berton & Mary Ellen, 1938-1941 (Box 3:, Folder 75)
  - Proctor, Gary, 1957-1974 (Box 3:, Folder 76)
  - Stam, Ben & Louise, 1939,1964 (Box 3:, Folder 77)
  - Vangelder, Enna & Fenna, 1941-1942 (Box 3:, Folder 78)
  - Vangelder, Enna, 1943-1950 (Box 3:, Folder 79)
  - Vangelder, Fenna, 1942-1954 (Box 3:, Folder 80)
  - Vangelder, Jack (Mr. & Mrs.), 1941-1950 (Box 3:, Folder 81)
  - David C. Kellems, II: Business, undated,1964-1974 (Box 3:, Folder 82)
  - Last Will and Testament of David and Tille Kellems, 1940-1943 (Box 3:, Folder 83)
  - Edgar E. Kellems Audit on Royalty Sales, 1951 (Box 3:, Folder 84)
  - Edgar E. Kellems Legal documents: will, contract), 1928-1953 (Box 3, Folder 85)
  - Oversize materials (from all series), undated (Box 52)
- Series II: Personal Papers, undated, 1883-1975
  - Kellems Co. Documents, 1928-1935 (Box 4:, Folder 85)
  - Last Will and Testament, 1929-1950 (Box 4:, Folder 86)
  - Correspondence regarding Last Will and Testament, 1931-1950 (Box 4:, Folder 87)
  - Taxi Crash, 1934 (Box 4:, Folder 88)
  - Arthur Peck, Lawyer, 1935-1952 (Box 4:, Folder 89)
  - Speeches, 1935-1937 (Box 4:, Folder 90)
  - B. Altman & Co., 1936, 1938, 1942 (Box 4:, Folder 91)
  - College, 1936, 1939-1941 (Box 4:, Folder 92)
  - Health, 1936, 1940-1941 (Box 4:, Folder 93)
  - A - Z, 1936 (Box 4:, Folder 94)
  - Wells Fargo & Co., 1936 (Box 4:, Folder 95)
  - Dogs, 1937-1942 (Box 4:, Folder 96)
  - A - Z, 1937 (Box 4:, Folder 97)
  - Foreign, 1937-1940 (Box 4:, Folder 98)
  - House, 1938-1941 (Box 4:, Folder 99)
  - Lawyers, 1938-1942 (Box 4:, Folder 100)
  - MC Call (Dogs), 1938 (Box 4:, Folder 101)
  - A - Z, 1938 (Box 4:, Folder 102)
  - Travels, 1938 (Box 4:, Folder 103)
  - Trip to Europe, 1938 (Box 4:, Folder 104)
  - Trip to South America, 1938 (Box 4:, Folder 105)
  - Vivien Kellems vs. Elsa Low, 1938-1943 (Box 4:, Folder 106)
  - Banks, 1939-1941 (Box 4:, Folder 107)
  - Correspondence with Stores, 1939-1940 (Box 4:, Folder 108)
  - Hotels, 1939-1940, 1950 (Box 4:, Folder 109)
  - Hutchinson Jewelry, 1939-1941 (Box 4:, Folder 110)
  - Julie Medlock, 1939-1941 (Box 4:, Folder 111)
  - Newspapers, 1939-1941 (Box 4:, Folder 112)
  - A - Z, 1939 (Box 4:, Folder 113)
  - Power, 1939-1941 (Box 4:, Folder 114)
  - Speeches, 1939, 1940, 1946 (Box 4:, Folder 115)
  - Travels, 1939 (Box 4:, Folder 116)
  - A - Z, 1940 (Box 4:, Folder 117)
  - Publishers, 1940-1941 (Box 4:, Folder 118)
  - Radio, 1940 (Box 4:, Folder 119)
  - Women, 1940-1942 (Box 4:, Folder 120)
  - Court, New York, 1941 (Box 4:, Folder 121)
  - A - Z, 1941 (Box 4:, Folder 122)
  - Publicity, 1941 (Box 4:, Folder 123)
  - Travel, 1941 (Box 4:, Folder 124)
  - A - Z, 1942 (Box 4:, Folder 125)
  - G - Mac, 1942 (Box 5:, Folder 126)
  - Ma - R, 1942 (Box 5:, Folder 127)
  - S - Z, 1942 (Box 5:, Folder 128)
  - A - C, 1943 (Box 5:, Folder 129)
  - D - K, 1943 (Box 5:, Folder 130)
  - K - M, 1943 (Box 5:, Folder 131)
  - N - Sm, 1943 (Box 5:, Folder 132)
  - Sin - Z, 1943 (Box 5:, Folder 133)
  - Attack by Congressman Coffee regarding Count Frederic von Zedlitz, 1944 (Box 5:, Folder 134)
  - A - Clark, 1944 (Box 5:, Folder 135)
  - Close - G, 1944 (Box 5:, Folder 136)
  - Dispute with Corbin and Bennett, 1944-1946 (Box 5:, Folder 137)
  - H - Lavelle, 1944 (Box 5:, Folder 138)
  - Lebereff - O, 1944 (Box 5:, Folder 139)
  - P - Silva, 1944 (Box 5:, Folder 140)
  - Simpson - Z, 1944 (Box 5:, Folder 141)
  - Christmas Cards, 1944-1943 (Box 5:, Folder 142)
  - C - E, 1945 (Box 6:, Folder 143)
  - F - J, 1945 (Box 6:, Folder 144)
  - K, 1945 (Box 6:, Folder 145)
  - L - Mc, 1945 (Box 6:, Folder 146)
  - M, 1945 (Box 6:, Folder 147)
  - N - Sig, 1945 (Box 6:, Folder 148)
  - Sil - Z, 1945 (Box 6:, Folder 149)
  - D - G, 1946 (Box 6:, Folder 150-151)
  - K - Mc, 1946 (Box 6:, Folder 152)
  - M - P, 1946 (Box 6:, Folder 153)
  - P - S, 1946 (Box 6:, Folder 154)
  - T - Z, 1946 (Box 6:, Folder 155)
  - D - G, 1947 (Box 6:, Folder 156)
  - Frederic von Zedlitz, 1947-1948 (Box 6:, Folder 157)
  - K - Mc, 1947 (Box 6:, Folder 158)
  - M - P, 1947 (Box 6:, Folder 159)
  - R - V, 1947 (Box 7:, Folder 160)
  - W - Z, 1947 (Box 7:, Folder 161)
  - A - C, 1948 (Box 7:, Folder 162)
  - D - J, 1948 (Box 7:, Folder 163)
  - K - Mc, 1948 (Box 7:, Folder 164)
  - M - Olsen, 1948 (Box 7:, Folder 165)
  - O - Z, 1948 (Box 7:, Folder 166)
  - Pasadena, California, 1948 (Box 7:, Folder 167)
  - Peck, NYC Attorney, 1948-1949 (Box 7:, Folder 168)
  - A - B, 1949 (Box 7:, Folder 169)
  - C - D, 1949 (Box 7:, Folder 170)
  - E - H, 1949 (Box 7:, Folder 171)
  - I - Mc, 1949 (Box 7:, Folder 172)
  - M - P, 1949 (Box 7:, Folder 173)
  - Powers of Attorney, 1949 (Box 7:, Folder 174)
  - Q - Z, 1949 (Box 7:, Folder 175)
  - W - Z, 1949-1950 (Box 8:, Folder 176)
  - Personal Letters, 1949 (Box 8:, Folder 177)
  - A - C, 1950 (Box 8:, Folder 178)
  - Benson, John B. Insurance, 1950-1953 (Box 8:, Folder 179)
  - D - K, 1950 (Box 8:, Folder 180)
  - Get well letters and cards (1 of 4), 1950 (Box 8:, Folder 181-184)
  - I. Miller and Sons, New York, 1950-1955 (Box 8:, Folder 185)
  - Personal Letters, 1950 (Box 8:, Folder 186)
  - L - P, 1950 (Box 8:, Folder 187)
  - R - Sch, 1950 (Box 8:, Folder 188)
  - Sch - V, 1950 (Box 8:, Folder 189)
  - A - Z, 1951 (Box 8:, Folder 190)
  - A - B, 1951 (Box 8:, Folder 191-192)
  - C, 1951 (Box 8:, Folder 193)
  - D - F, 1951 (Box 8:, Folder 194)
  - G - K, 1951 (Box 8:, Folder 195)
  - L - Mc, 1951 (Box 8:, Folder 196)
  - M - P, 1951 (Box 8:, Folder 197)
  - Q - S, 1951 (Box 8:, Folder 198)
  - T - Z, 1951 (Box 8:, Folder 199)
  - Alabama - California, 1952-1953 (Box 9:, Folder 200)
  - Caxton Press, 1952-1953 (Box 9:, Folder 201)
  - Connecticut, 1952-1953 (Box 9:, Folder 202-203)
  - Delaware - Georgia, 1952-1953 (Box 9:, Folder 204-205)
  - Foreign, 1952-1953 (Box 9:, Folder 206)
  - Idaho - Kentucky, 1952-1953 (Box 9:, Folder 207-208)
  - Louisiana - Nebraska, 1952-1953 (Box 9:, Folder 209)
  - New York, A - M, 1952-1953 (Box 9:, Folder 210-211)
  - New York, N - Z, 1952-1953 (Box 9:, Folder 212)
  - Nevada - New Mexico, 1952-1953 (Box 9:, Folder 213)
  - North Carolina - Ohio, 1952-1953 (Box 9:, Folder 214)
  - Ohio, 1952-1953 (Box 9:, Folder 215)
  - Oklahoma - Oregon, 1952-1953 (Box 9:, Folder 216)
  - Texas, 1952-1953 (Box 10:, Folder 217-218)
  - Pennsylvania - Wisconsin, 1952-1953 (Box 10:, Folder 219-221)
  - Address Lists, 1953-1956 (Box 10:, Folder 222)
  - Trip to Europe, 1953-1955 (Box 10:, Folder 223)
  - Address Lists, 1954-1955 (Box 10:, Folder 224)
  - Alabama - Colorado, 1954 (Box 10:, Folder 225)
  - Connecticut, 1954 (Box 10:, Folder 226-227)
  - Delaware - Illinois, 1954 (Box 10:, Folder 228-229)
  - Foreign, 1954 (Box 10:, Folder 230)
  - Mexico Trip, 1954-1955 (Box 10:, Folder 231)
  - Indiana - New Mexico, 1954 (Box 10:, Folder 232)
  - New York, 1954 (Box 10:, Folder 233-234)
  - North Carolina - Wyoming, 1954 (Box 10:, Folder 235-236)
  - Alabama - Colorado, 1955 (Box 11:, Folder 237)
  - Connecticut, 1955 (Box 11:, Folder 238-240)
  - Delaware - New Jersey, 1955 (Box 11:, Folder 241-243)
  - Materials Ordered, 1955 (Box 11:, Folder 244)
  - Ohio - Foreign, 1955 (Box 11:, Folder 245-246)
  - New York, 1955 (Box 11:, Folder 247-249)
  - A - California, 1956 (Box 11:, Folder 250-252)
  - Connecticut, 1956 (Box 11:, Folder 253-255)
  - D - M, 1956 (Box 11:, Folder 256-258)
  - N, 1956 (Box 12:, Folder 259-261)
  - O - Foreign, 1956 (Box 12:, Folder 262-263)
  - Pitnam Electric Products Company, 1956-1958 (Box 12:, Folder 264)
  - Alabama - Colorado, 1957 (Box 12:, Folder 265)
  - California, 1957-1958 (Box 12:, Folder 266)
  - Connecticut and Rhode Island, 1957 (Box 12:, Folder 267-270)
  - Delaware - New Jersey, 1957 (Box 12:, Folder 271-273)
  - Map of Rome and Letter Writing, 1957-1958 (Box 12:, Folder 274)
  - Materials Ordered, 1957 (Box 12:, Folder 275)
  - New York, 1957 (Box 12:, Folder 276-278)
  - Ohio - Sweden, 1957 (Box 12:, Folder 279-280)
  - River Road Property, 1957-1960 (Box 12:, Folder 281)
  - Travel, 1957 (Box 13:, Folder 282)
  - Travel, 1957-1958 (Box 13:, Folder 283)
  - Trip to Europe, Africa, and India, 1957 (Box 13:, Folder 284)
  - Alabama - Arkansas, 1958 (Box 13:, Folder 285)
  - Connecticut, 1958 (Box 13:, Folder 286-287)
  - Delaware - Washington D.C., 1958 (Box 13:, Folder 288)
  - Florida, Georgia, Arizona, 1958 (Box 13:, Folder 289)
  - Foreign, 1958 (Box 13:, Folder 290)
  - Idaho - Iowa, 1958, 1960 (Box 13:, Folder 291)
  - India Business, 1958-1959 (Box 13:, Folder 292)
  - Kansas, 1958 (Box 13:, Folder 293)
  - M, 1958 (Box 13:, Folder 294)
  - Materials Ordered, 1958 (Box 13:, Folder 295)
  - McGraw-Hill Companies, Monthly Reports, 1958 (Box 13:, Folder 296)
  - N, 1958 (Box 13:, Folder 297)
  - New York, 1958 (Box 13:, Folder 298-300)
  - Ohio - Pennsylvania, 1958 (Box 13:, Folder 301)
  - O - Washington, 1958-1959 (Box 13:, Folder 302)
  - Rhode Island - Virginia, 1958 (Box 13:, Folder 303)
  - Switzerland, Aprons, 1958, 1960, 1962 (Box 13:, Folder 304)
  - West Virginia, Wisconsin, Canada, 1958 (Box 13:, Folder 305)
  - Alabama, Arkansas, Rhode Island, Tennessee, Arizona, Texas, 1959 (Box 13:, Folder 306)
  - California, 1959 (Box 13:, Folder 307)
  - California Trip, Homer's Funeral, 1959 (Box 13:, Folder 308)
  - Connecticut, 1959 (Box 13:, Folder 309-310)
  - Colonel Homer F. Kellems, 1959 (Box 14:, Folder 311)
  - Washington D.C., 1959 (Box 14:, Folder 312)
  - Foreign, 1959 (Box 14:, Folder 313)
  - Florida, Georgia, Illinois, Indiana, Iowa, Kansas, North Carolina, 1959 (Box 14:, Folder 314)
  - M - N, 1959 (Box 14:, Folder 315)
  - New Jersey and New Mexico, 1959 (Box 14:, Folder 316)
  - New York, 1959 (Box 14:, Folder 317-318)
  - Utah, Vermont, Virginia, 1959 (Box 14:, Folder 319)
  - W, 1959 (Box 14:, Folder 320)
  - A - L, 1960 (Box 14:, Folder 321)
  - Connecticut, 1960 (Box 14:, Folder 322-323)
  - Foreign, 1960 (Box 14:, Folder 324)
  - M, 1960 (Box 14:, Folder 325)
  - N - V, 1960 (Box 14:, Folder 326)
  - New York, 1960 (Box 14:, Folder 327-329)
  - W, 1960 (Box 14:, Folder 330)
  - A - C, 1962 (Box 15:, Folder 331)
  - Connecticut, 1962 (Box 15:, Folder 332-338)
  - Washington D.C., 1962 (Box 15:, Folder 339)
  - Florida - Idaho, 1962 (Box 15:, Folder 340)
  - Foreign, 1962 (Box 15:, Folder 341)
  - Illinois - M, 1962 (Box 15:, Folder 342)
  - New Jersey, 1962 (Box 15:, Folder 343)
  - New York, 1962 (Box 15:, Folder 344-345)
  - N - W, 1962 (Box 15:, Folder 346)
  - Rhode Island, 1962 (Box 15:, Folder 347)
  - A - C, 1963 (Box 16:, Folder 348)
  - Connecticut, 1963-1964 (Box 16:, Folder 349-351)
  - Washington D.C., 1963-1964 (Box 16:, Folder 352)
  - Florida and Georgia, 1963-1964 (Box 16:, Folder 353)
  - Foreign, 1963-1964 (Box 16:, Folder 354)
  - H - I, 1963-1964 (Box 16:, Folder 355)
  - M - N, 1963-1964 (Box 16:, Folder 356)
  - New York, 1963-1964 (Box 16:, Folder 357-358)
  - O, 1963-1964 (Box 16:, Folder 359)
  - Pennsylvania, 1963-1964 (Box 16:, Folder 360)
  - Tax Forms, 1963-1964 (Box 16:, Folder 361)